<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>

    <string name="category_historic_places">Historic</string>

    <string name="category_islamic_places">Islamic</string>

    <string name="category_christian_places">Christian</string>

    <string name="category_modern">Modern</string>

    <string name="pyramids">Pyramids</string>

    <string name="abu_simble_temple">Abu Simple Temple</string>

    <string name="citadel_of_qaitbay">Citadel of Quaitbay</string>

    <string name="luxor_temple">Luxor Temple</string>

    <string name="philae_temple">Philae Temple</string>

    <string name="valley_kings">Vally of the Kings</string>

    <string name="karnak_temple">Karnak Temple</string>

    <string name="edfu_temple">Edfu Temple</string>

    <string name="al_azhar">Al Azhar</string>

    <string name="salah_citadel">Salah El Din Citadel</string>

    <string name="amr_mosque">Mosque of Amr ibn Al-Aas</string>

    <string name="tulun_mosque">Mosque of Ahmed ibn Tulun</string>

    <string name="hanging_church">The Hanging Church</string>

    <string name="catherine_monastery">Saint Catherine Monastery</string>

    <string name="wadi_el_natrun">Wadi El-Natrun Monastery</string>

    <string name="white_monastery">White Monastery</string>

    <string name="cairo_tower">Cairo Tower</string>

    <string name="egyptian_museum">Egyptian Museum</string>

    <string name="khan_el_khalili">Khan El-Khalili</string>

    <string name="abdeen_palace">Abdeen Palace</string>

    <string name="location">Location</string>

    <!-- Description of the great Pyramids -->
    <string name="pyramids_description">
        "The Great Pyramid of Giza is a huge pyramid built by the Ancient Egyptians. It stands in Giza,
        Egypt. It is the oldest of the Seven Wonders of the Ancient World, and the only one to remain
        mostly intact. When it was built it was 146.5 metres (481 feet) tall. It was the tallest building
        in the world for over 3,800 years."
    </string>

    <!-- Description of Abu simbel temple -->>
    <string name="abu_simbel_description">
        "The Abu Simbel temples are two very large rock temples built by the ancient Egyptians, at
        Abu Simbel. This is a village in Nubia, southern Egypt. The temples were cut into solid rock
        in side of a cliff during the reign of Pharaoh Ramesses II in the 13th century BC."
    </string>

    <!-- Description of The Citadel of Qaitbay -->
    <string name="qaitbay_description">
        "The Citadel of Qaitbay (or the Fort of Qaitbay) is a 15th-century defensive fortress located
        on the Mediterranean sea coast, in Alexandria, Egypt. It was established in 1477 AD (882 AH)
        by Sultan Al-Ashraf Sayf al-Din Qa'it Bay. The Citadel is situated on the eastern side of the
        northern tip of Pharos Island at the mouth of the Eastern Harbour."
    </string>

    <!-- Description of Luxor temple -->
    <string name="luxor_temple_description">
        "Luxor Temple is a large Ancient Egyptian temple complex located on the east bank of the
        Nile River in the city today known as Luxor (ancient Thebes) and was constructed from 1100 BC-1600 BC."
    </string>

    <!-- Description of Philae temple -->
    <string name="philae_description">
        "Philae is currently an island in the reservoir of the Aswan Low Dam, downstream of the Aswan
        Dam and Lake Nasser. Philae was originally located near the expansive First Cataract of the
        Nile in Upper Egypt and was the site of an Egyptian temple complex. These rapids and the
        surrounding area have been variously flooded since the initial construction of the Aswan Low
        Dam in 1902. The temple complex was later dismantled and relocated to nearby Agilkia Island."
    </string>

    <!-- Description of The Vally of the Kings -->
    <string name="valley_kings_description">
        "The Valley of the Kings is a valley in Egypt where, for a period of nearly 500 years from the
        16th to 11th century BC, rock cut tombs were excavated for the Pharaohs and powerful nobles
        of the New Kingdom (the Eighteenth to the Twentieth Dynasties of Ancient Egypt)."
    </string>

    <!-- Description of Karnak temple -->
    <string name="karnak_temple_description">
        "The Temple of Karnak is the largest Temple in the World! The complex contains a group of Temples
        such as the Great Temple of Amon Ra, The Temple of Khonso, The Ipt Temple, The Temple of Ptah,
        the Temple of Montho and the Temple of the God Osiris. A 20m high, mud brick enclosure wall,
        surrounded all of these buildings."
    </string>

    <!-- Description of Edfu temple -->
    <string name="edfu_temple_description">
        "The Temple of Edfu is an ancient Egyptian temple, located on the west bank of the Nile in Edfu,
        Upper Egypt. After the chief god Horus-Apollo. It is one of the best preserved shrines in Egypt.
        The temple, dedicated to the falcon god Horus, was built in the Ptolemaic period between 237 and 57 BC."
    </string>

    <!-- Description of Al Azhar Mosque -->
    <string name="al_azhar_description">
        "Al-Azhar Mosque is an Egyptian mosque in Islamic Cairo. Al-Mu'izz li-Din Allah of the Fatimid
        dynasty commissioned its construction for the newly established capital city in 970. Its name
        is usually thought to allude to the Islamic prophet Muhammad's daughter Fatimah. It was the
        first mosque established in Cairo, a city that has since gained the nickname "the City of a Thousand Minarets."
    </string>

    <!-- Description of Salah El-Din Citadel -->
    <string name="salah_citadel_description">
        "The Saladin Citadel of Cairo is a medieval Islamic fortification in Cairo, Egypt. The location,
        on Mokattam hill near the center of Cairo. It is now a preserved historic site, with mosques
        and museums. In 1976, it was proclaimed by UNESCO as a part of the World Heritage Site Historic."
    </string>

    <!-- Description of Mosque of Amr ibn Al-Aas -->
    <string name="amr_mosque_description">
        "The Mosque of Amr ibn al-As was originally built in 641–642 AD, as the center of the newly
        founded capital of Egypt, Fustat. The original structure was the first mosque ever built in
        Egypt and the whole of Africa. The location for the mosque was the site of the tent of the
        commander of the Muslim army, general Amr ibn al-As."
    </string>

    <!-- Description of Mosque of Ahmed ibn Tulun -->
    <string name="tulun_mosque_description">
        "The Mosque of Ibn Tulun, is considered the second oldest mosque extant in Egypt. It is
        established in AH 256 / AD 870 as the capital of the Tulunid state in Egypt. The floor plan
        of the mosque assumes the form of a square, measuring approximately 26,318 sqm."
    </string>

    <!-- Description of The Hanging church -->
    <string name="hanging_church_description">
        "The Hanging Church is considered the oldest church in the area of Al-Fustat (Old Cairo).
        It is known as Al-Muallaka (the hanging) because it was built on the ruins of two old towers
        that remained from an old fortress called the Fortress of Babylon. It was dedicated to The
        Virgin Mary and St. Dimiana."
    </string>

    <!-- Description of Saint Catherine Monastery -->
    <string name="saint_catherine_description">
        "Saint Catherine's Monastery lies on the Sinai Peninsula, at the mouth of a gorge at the foot
        of Mount Sinai, in the city of Saint Catherine,in South Sinai. Built between 548 and 565,
        the monastery is one of the oldest working Christian monasteries in the world. The site contains
        the world's oldest continually operating library."
    </string>

    <!-- Description of Wadi El-Natrun Monastery -->
    <string name="wadi_el_natrun_description">
        "Wadi El Natrun is a valley located in Beheira, Egypt. is one of the three early Christian
        monastic centers located in the desert of the northwestern Nile Delta. The other two monastic
        centers are Nitria and Kellia."
    </string>

    <!-- Description of White Monastery -->
    <string name="white_monastery_description">
        "The Coptic White Monastery is located near the Upper Egyptian city of Sohag, and about two
        and a half miles (4km) south-east of the Red Monastery. The name of the monastery is derived
        from the colour of the white limestone of its outside walls. The White Monastery is architecturally
        similar to the Red Monastery."
    </string>

    <!-- Description of Cairo tower -->
    <string name="cairo_tower_description">
        "The Cairo Tower is a free-standing concrete tower located in Cairo, Egypt. At 187 m (614 ft),
        it has been the tallest structure in Egypt and North Africa for about 50 years. It was the
        tallest structure in Africa for 10 years, until 1971 when it was surpassed by Hillbrow Tower
        in South Africa."
    </string>

    <!-- Description of Egyptian Museum -->
    <string name="egyptian_museum_description">
        "Egyptian Museum is home to an extensive collection of ancient Egyptian antiquities. It has
        120,000 items, with a representative amount on display, the remainder in storerooms. The
        edifice is one of the largest museums in the region. As of July 2017, the museum is open
        to the public."
    </string>

    <!-- Description of Khan El-Khalili -->
    <string name="khan_el_khalili_description">
        "The Khan el-Khalili today is mainly occupied by Egyptian merchants and shopholders, but is
        significantly geared towards tourists. Shops typically sell souvenirs, antiques and jewellery,
        but many traditional workshops continue to operate in the surrounding area and the adjoining
        goldsmiths' souq, for example, is still important for locals."
    </string>

    <!-- Description of Abdeen Palace -->
    <string name="abdeen_palace_description">
        "In 1863 Khedive Ismail Pasha began constructing Abdeen Palace as the seat of his government
        and a symbol of Egypt's strength. It was a royal residence until the end of the monarchy in
        1952 and is still used by the president for official events."
    </string>
</resources>
